Guide to the University Archives Photograph Collection, Glass Negatives and Lantern Slides, circa 1890-circa 1960 UA 023.031 UA 023.031
Special Collections Research Center
University Archives Photograph Collection, Glass Negatives and Lantern Slides
circa 1890-circa 1960
UA 023.031
Special Collections Research Center
9.5 Linear feet
This collection consists of glass negatives and lantern slides chiefly depicting various aspects of agriculture in North Carolina and buildings on the campus of N.C. State University. Subjects include agricultural extension work, agricultural research, farms and farm life, animal husbandry, botany, horticulture, and crop science. One set of slides shows the university's first nuclear reactor; another comprises song slides that were presumably used at 4-H meetings or camps in the state. Many of the slides are hand-colored. Also included in the collection are photographic prints made from some of the negatives, manuscript material from the original storage containers, and examples of the original storage envelopes.
The North Carolina College of Agricultural and Mechanic Arts was founded as the state's land-grant institution in 1887, and formally opened its doors two years later. Renamed the North Carolina State College of Agriculture and Engineering in 1917, the school became part of the Consolidated University of North Carolina (later the University of North Carolina System) in 1932. The institution was restyled North Carolina State of the University of North Carolina at Raleigh in 1963, and two years later renamed North Carolina State University (officially the North Carolina State University at Raleigh).
19 boxes
North Carolina State University. University Archives.
Restrictions to Access
This collection is open for research; access requires at least 24 hours advance notice.
Acquisitions Information
This collection was created by the University Archives.
Historical Note
The North Carolina College of Agricultural and Mechanic Arts was founded as the state's land-grant institution in 1887, and formally opened its doors two years later. In 1917, the school was renamed the North Carolina State College of Agriculture and Engineering, reflecting its broadened instructional and research activities. The college's extension program was established in 1914, and a major reorganization of the institution occurred in 1923, with the creation of schools over its fields of study.
In 1932, "State College," as it was known, greatly reworked its curricula upon becoming part of the Consolidated University of North Carolina (later the University of North Carolina System). Undergoing unparalleled growth in size and academic programs after the Second World War, the school took on a new designation appropriate to its degree-granting and research status in 1963, when it was restyled North Carolina State of the University of North Carolina at Raleigh. Two years later, the institution was renamed North Carolina State University (officially the North Carolina State University at Raleigh).
In another key administrative change, the university's schools were redesignated colleges in 1987. That same year saw the ground breaking of the institution's Centennial Campus, a major center of academic, corporate, and governmental research. By 2007, N.C. State had a student body of over 31,000 and a faculty of nearly 2,000.
For more online information, see a Brief History of North Carolina State University and Historical Sketch of North Carolina State University.
Scope and Content Note
This collection consists of glass negatives and lantern slides chiefly depicting various aspects of agriculture in North Carolina and buildings on the campus of North Carolina State University. Subjects include agricultural extension work, agricultural research, farms and farm life, animal husbandry, botany, horticulture, and crop science. One set of slides shows the university's first nuclear reactor; another comprises song slides that were presumably used at 4-H meetings or camps in the state. Many of the slides are hand-colored. Much of the material was created by or received from the Agricultural Extension Service, the Departments of Engineering Research and Electrical and Computer Engineering, and the School of Physical and Mathematical Sciences. Some sets were numbered in previous processing efforts. Original groupings have generally been maintained in the physical arrangement, but broken or cracked negatives and plates have been separated. Also included in the collection are photographic prints made from some of the negatives, manuscript material from the original storage containers, and examples of the original storage envelopes.
Organization of the Collection
This collection is divided into the following series:
Agriculture
Athletics
Buildings and Structures
Charts and Graphs
Forests and Woods
4-H Clubs
North Carolina State University Campus
People
Water and Dams
Photographic Prints and Manuscript Material
Related Material
University Archives Photograph Collection, Agriculture and Life Sciences (College of) Photographs, UA 023.006
University Archives Photograph Collection, Athletics Photographs (UA 023.004)
University Archives Photograph Collection, Campus Facilities and Views (UA 023.005)
University Archives Photograph Collection, 4-H Youth Development Photographs (UA 023.008)
North Carolina State University--Buildings.; North Carolina State University--History.; 4-H clubs--North Carolina; 4-H clubs--Songs and music; Agricultural extension work--North Carolina; Agriculture--North Carolina; Agriculture--Research--North Carolina; Agriculture--Study and teaching (Higher)--North Carolina; Agronomy--North Carolina; Animal culture--North Carolina; Botany--Study and teaching (Higher)--North Carolina; Crop science--North Carolina; Dry plate negatives; Engineering--Research--North Carolina; Farm buildings--North Carolina; Farm life--North Carolina; Horticulture--North Carolina; Lantern slides; Livestock--North Carolina; Nuclear engineering--North Carolina; Photographic prints; Wet collodion negatives
- Agriculture, Series 1
  - Apples
    - Sules V-B on Apple [3] - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 31)
  - Cabbages
    - (no. 13) Eastern Carolina, North Carolina - Diec - cabbage and treated - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 10)
    - (no. 14) Avery County, North Carolina - Field of good cabbage yield of DNC ton per acre - people, cars, and barns in the background - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 11)
  - Cacti
    - Cactus bloom (122) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 22)
    - Cactus bloom [5] - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 33)
  - Cantaloupes
    - Cantaloupe breeding - F. generation vine and fruit of cross between netted gem female and white spine cucumber male - photo 6 August 1900 - L. R. D. (22) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 24)
    - Cantaloupe breeding - F. fruits of netted gem female x white spine cucumber male - fruits are smooth on outside and cucumber like on the inside - no seed cavities in these fruits - L. R. D. - photo 6 August 1900 (24) - Grape Study - Set #17 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 25)
    - Cantaloupe breeding - photo 6 August 1900 - F. fruits (immature) of netted gem female x white spine cucumber - fruits at this stage are but very little ovules - L. R. D. - Grape Study - Set #1 (Cardbox 6, Envelope 28)
  - Cattle
    - Cattle loading ramp - Agriculture School Buildings (Farm) - Train cars - Atlantic Coast Line (Cardbox 1, Envelope 2)
    - Cattle loading ramp - Train cars - 10/1929 (Cardbox 1, Envelope 3)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 28)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 29)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 30)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 31)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 32)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 33)
    - Cattle (Cardbox 1, Envelope 34)
    - Cow and barn, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 35)
    - Cow and barn, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 36)
    - Group of cows, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 37)
    - Group of cows, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 38)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 39)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 40)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 41)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 42)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 43)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 44)
    - Cow and campus, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 45)
    - Group of cattle, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 46)
    - Group of cattle, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 47)
    - Cattle in barn, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 48)
    - Cattle, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 49)
    - Cow, Set #13 (Cardbox 2, Envelope 50)
    - Cattle - June 1917 - dipping vat, Iredell County, side and end view of galvanized vat, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 3)
    - Cattle - June 1917 - dipping vat, Iredell County, side and end view of galvanized vat, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 4)
    - Cattle - June 1917 - C. V. Farm - "permanent" loading chute, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 5)
    - Cattle - 19 March 1929 - the scrub bull "George" - Wenona, number 5, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 36)
    - Cattle - 19 March 1929 - Wenona, number 4, native calves, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 7)
    - Cattle - 26 May 1932 - Vitamin A studies with beef cattle, Central Experiment Station - heifer number 7 before slaughter, number 32B, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 8)
    - Cattle - 4 September 1936 - cow herd - Wenona, number 21, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 9)
    - Cows in a pasture - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 73)
    - Cows in a field - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 126)
    - Black walnut trees, cattle in field - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 127)
    - Group of people in stands with two men and a cow in the front - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 128)
    - Good pasture for milk cow - people and cows in a field - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 129)
    - People and cows in a field in a hilly region - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 130)
    - Farm - barns and field with cows - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 131)
    - People in stands with man milking cow in front - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 132)
    - Men with cows and milk buckets between stands of people in front of a church - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 133)
    - Man and two cows on a hillside - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 134)
    - 4-H Calf Club, circa 1920-1930s - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 135)
    - Bull in a field with mountain in the background - Hand Colored Slides, Animals (Cardbox 12, Envelope 136)
    - Animal Science - Dairy - The little fellows enjoy handling good stock grown on good permanent pastures. S. S. Sawyer's Farm - two children with a cow and calf - 6 - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research (Cardbox 13, Envelope 1)
    - Cow (broken negative) (Cardbox 17, Envelope 3)
  - Corn
    - Corn field (small hole in emulsion of negative) (Cardbox 1, Envelope 1)
    - Corn - Major McKinley Freeman's Prize Acres, 1914, Buncombe, County, North Carolina - Left - E.D. Weaver, Farm Demonstrator - Right - N. Buckner, Secretary, Board of Trade, Asheville, North Carolina - Set #15 (Cardbox 4, Envelope 7)
    - Types of ears - 6 July 1906 - 9 Butler's Prolific, 10 Square Deal, 11 Brakes - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 2)
    - Types of kernels 7 July 1906 - 1 Cocke's Prolific, 2 Weekley's Improved, 3 Shellem's Prolific, 4 Bigg's Seven Ear, 5 Hickory King, 6 Wilson's Success, 7 Thomas' Improved, 8 Farmer's Favorite, 9 Butler's Prolific, 10 Square Deal, 11 Brakes - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 3)
    - Types of ears 7 July 1906 - 1 Cocke's Prolific, 2 Weekley's Improved, 3 Shellems Prolific, 4 Biggs Prolific (or Seven Ear) - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 4)
    - Types of ears 7 July 1906 - 5 Hickory King, 6 Wilson's Success, 7 Thomas' Improved, 8 Farmer's Favorite - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 5)
    - Types of kernels 7 July 1906 - Read with points down - 12 Holt's Strawberry, 13 Mosby's Prolific, 14 Sander's Improved, 15 Southern Beauty, 16 Eureka, 17 Hasting's Prolific, 18 Section #77, 19 Iowa Silver Mine, 20 Boone County White, 21 Reid's Yellow Dent, 22 Riley's Favorite, 23 Leaming Yellow - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 6)
    - Types of ears 23 April 1907 - 4 Southern Beauty, 5 Eureka, 6 Mosby's Prolific, 7 Sander's Improved - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 7)
    - Types of ears 23 April 1907 - Reds Yellow Dent, 9 Riley's Favorite, 10 Iowa Silver Mine, 11 Selection 77 - 2 copies of negative (one is slightly cracked) - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 8)
    - Types of ears 23 April 1907 - 15 Wyatt's Improved Yellow, 16 Hasting's Prolific, 17 Marlboro Prolific, 18 Cocke's Prolific (Tenn.) - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 9)
    - Types of ears 23 April 1907 - 19 Hickory King (Tenn.), 20 American Queen, 21 Parker's Cocke's Prolific, 22 Bradbury's Improved - 2 copies of the negative - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 10)
    - Types of ears 23 April 1907 - 19 Hickory King (Tenn.), 20 American Queen, 21 Parker's Cocke's Prolific - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 11)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 1 Peele's Prolific, 2 Cooper's Improved, 3 Whelchel's Dent, 4 Harris Improved (emulsion deteriorating in small curved pattern) - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 12)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 5 Farmer's Favorite, 6 Osborne, 7 Krinninger's Improved, 8 Williams (negative badly chipped in lower left corner) - See cracked/broken negatives - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 13)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 9 Horsetooth, 10 Thomas Improved, 11 Fredonia's Pride, 12 Cleveland's Pure White - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 14)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 13 Wright's Improved, 14 Jones' White, 15 Columbia Beauty, 16 Goodman's Prolific - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 15)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 17 MacAuley's White Dent, 18 Hickory King (Va.), 19 Jackson's White Cap Prolific, 20 Sharber's - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 16)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 17 MacAuley's White Dent, 18 Hickory King (Va.), 19 Jackson's White Cap Prolific, 20 Sharber's - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 17)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 21 Hildreth Yellow Dent, 22 Jones Yellow Dent, 23 Kansas Sunflower, 24 Learning Yellow - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 18)
    - Types of ears 29 July 1909 - 25 Brakes, 26 Biggs Seven Ear, 27 Culpepper's Extra Prolific, 28 Dodson's Shoepeg Prolific - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 19)
    - Various kernel types 29 July 1909 - Read with points down - 1 Kansas Sunflower, 2 Jones Yellow Dent, 3 Hildreth's Yellow Dent, 4 Wyatt's Improved Yellow, 5 Sharbers, 6 Hickory King (Va.), 7 Culpepper's Extra Prolific, 8 Goodman's Prolific, 9 Columbia Beauty, 10 Jones White, 11 Wright's Improved, 12 Dodson's Shoepeg Prolific - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 20)
    - Various kernel types 29 July 1909 - Read with points up - 1 Horsetooth, 2 Henry Grady, 3 MacAuleys White Dent, 4 Osborne, 5 Whelchel's Dent, 6 Krinninger's Improved, 7 Jackson's White Cap Prolific, 8 Cleveland's Pure White, 9 Fridonia's Pride, 10 Williams, 11 Peele's Prolific, 12 Harris' Improved, 13 Poole's, 14 MacMackin's Gourd Seed, 15 Cooper's Improved, 16 Fry's Improved, 17 Bradbury's Improved, 18 Cleckler's Improved (emulsion deteriorating badly) - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 21)
    - "A and E College Sweepstakes, Corn Show February 1921," an ear of corn. (Bottom right corner is chipped) - Central Farm Corn (Cardbox 7, Envelope 22)
    - Corn - Buncombe County Corn show - 1914 - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research (Cardbox 13, Envelope 3)
    - Group of boys standing in a field two are holding corn - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 180)
    - Demonstration in judging of corn for exhibition - US Dept. Of Agriculture - S. 109 #54 Neg. No. 12792-B - Hand Colored Slides, agricultural ext. & research, Set #19 (Cardbox 13, Envelope 8)
    - Corn - Central Farm - 29 July 1909 (negative badly chipped in lower left corner) - types of ears 5 - Farmer's favorite, 6 - Osborne, 7 - Krinminger's Improved, 8 - Williams (Cardbox 17, Envelope 13)
  - Crops
    - Grass treated with phos. And untreated - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 160)
    - Lespedupa treated with phos. And untreated - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 161)
    - Wheat treated with phos. And untreated - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 162)
    - Four bunches of grass or grain - different sizes - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 163)
    - Orchard grass treated with phos. and untreated - man in front of a car holding two bundles of grass - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 164)
    - Man and two piles of corn - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 165)
    - Man with 2 piles of corn used in experiment with Linux pho. - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 166)
    - Oats treated with phos. And untreated - Hand Colored Slides, Crops - treated/untreated (Cardbox 13, Envelope 167)
  - Enclosures
    - Small penned in area - 12/1929 (Cardbox 1, Envelope 5)
    - Small penned in area (negative is slightly chipped) (Cardbox 1, Envelope 6)
    - General - C. V. Farm - June 1917 - "temporary" loading chute, Animal Husbandry (Cardbox 3, Envelope 2)
  - Farm Equipment
    - Tractor and ramp on a hillside - Hand Colored Slides, Various (Cardbox 12, Envelope 155)
  - Fields and Land
    - (no. 3) Macon Co, North Carolina - Erosion on fresh plowed land - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 1)
    - (no. 4) Macon County, North Carolina - Land from 1 (no. 3) after treatment (paper edge is ripped) - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 2)
    - (no. 5) Watauga County, North Carolina - Healing of Gullies with straw and black locust - same as 4 (no. 6) and 5 (no. 7) - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 3)
    - (no. 6) Watauga County, North Carolina - Same as 3 (no. 5) and 5 (no. 7) - Close view of straw and locust - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 4)
    - (no. 7) Watauga County, North Carolina - same as 3 (no. 5) and 4 (no. 6) after 2 years treatment with phos. lime, grass, trees - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 5)
    - (no. 16) Watauga, North Carolina - Hill land well protected cove creek watershed - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 12)
    - (no. 17) Watauga County - Dr. Perry Farm land - well protected by Good Management - North Carolina - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 13)
    - (no. 17A) Watauga County - Dr. Perry Farm land (same as 13 (no. 17)) (slide is broken, tape loose on right side) - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 14)
    - (no. 17B)Watauga County, North Carolina - good meadow land - Dr. Perry farm - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 15)
    - (no. 18) Watauga County - Cove Creek area - Good land use - North Carolina (paper torn on left side) - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 16)
    - (no. 19) Avery County, North Carolina - Pasture needs plant food - person standing in field (slide is cracked) - See broken/cracked slides 15.17 - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series - No. 19 (Cardbox 10, Envelope 17)
    - (no. 21) Madison County, North Carolina - strip cropping mountains - 2 children - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 19)
    - (no. 23) Macon County, North Carolina - What happens when no cover on hills - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 21)
    - (no. 24) Madison County, North Carolina - row crops move off the hills - tobacco field - man in field - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 22)
    - (no. 25) Avery County, North Carolina - crimson clover treated with TVA phos. - 2 men in a field, circa 1920s - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 23)
    - (no. 26) Yancey County, North Carolina - check plot on past where phos. gee applied - Hand Colored Slides, Numbered Series (Cardbox 10, Envelope 24)
    - Field with flowers and stalk - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 67)
    - Field with grass and stalks in the mountains, building in the background - Hand Colored Slides, H. C. initials (Cardbox 11, Envelope 68)
    - Barn, fields and a row of flowers with mountains in the background - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 74)
    - Haystacks - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 75)
    - Ship cropping on hill - land provides protection - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 76)
    - Field and building - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 77)
    - Field with sticks placed in rows - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 78)
    - Field with flowers - building in the background in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 79)
    - Fields and a farm near the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 80)
    - Fields and home below a hill - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 81)
    - Field with house - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 82)
    - Two haystacks in a field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 83)
    - Field and farm in a hilly region - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 84)
    - Fields, stream and mountains, no. 212A, neg. Nc-23 (slide is cracked) - see broken and cracked negatives and slides 15.85 - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 85)
    - Field, trees, and house on a hillside (slide is cracked) - see broken and cracked negatives and slides 15.86 - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 86)
    - Field and stream - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 87)
    - Fields and house in mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 88)
    - Field, stream, road and building in the mountains (see 90) - new stream channel cut by not keeping banks clean - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 89)
    - Field, stream, road and building in the mountains (duplicate of 89) - new stream channel cut by not keeping banks clean - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 90)
    - Field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 91)
    - Field and houses in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 92)
    - Field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 93)
    - Fields and farm in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 94)
    - Field in the mountains (slide has grainy substance on back) - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 95)
    - Field, house and farm in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 96)
    - Field in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 97)
    - Field and building in the mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 98)
    - Field - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 11, Envelope 99)
    - Field in mountains - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 100)
    - Field and trees - Hand Colored Slides, Fields (Cardbox 12, Envelope 101)